Astonishing. Intimate. Definitive.
Ronaldo is a documentary, history film directed by Anthony Wonke.
Filmed over 14 months with unprecedented access into the inner circle of the man and the sport, this is the
first official and fully authorised film of one of the most celebrated figures in football.
For the first time ever, the world gets vividly candid and un-paralleled, behind-closed-doors access to
the footballer, father, family-man and friend in this moving & fascinating documentary.
Through in-depth conversations, state of the art football footage and never before seen archival footage, the film gives an astonishing
insight into the sporting and personal life of triple Ballon D'Or winner Cristiano Ronaldo at the peak of his career.
From the makers of ‘Senna’ and ‘Amy’, Ronaldo takes audiences on an intimate and revealing
journey of what it’s like to live as an iconic athlete in the eye of the storm.
Self, played by Cristiano Ronaldo.
Self, played by Lionel Messi.
Self, played by Dolores Aveiro.
Self, played by Hugo Aveiro.
English Sports Presenter 1 (voice), played by Georgie Bingham.
English Sports Presenter 2 (voice), played by Adrian Clarke.
Ronaldo is a 2015 British documentary film directed by Anthony Wonke.
It tells the life and career of Portuguese
professional footballer Cristiano Ronaldo.
The film was released worldwide on 9 November 2015.
A trailer for the film was released on 28 September 2015.
The film explores themes of sports, biography,
football (soccer), sports documentary.
The tone is emotional.